<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>The Paranoid Tip - other</title>
      <link>https://orbitofdeceit.github.io</link>
      <description>Magnet for tweet bots, unwanted social media gurus and online marketing</description>
      <generator>Zola</generator>
      <language>en</language>
      <atom:link href="https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/categories/other/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
      <item>
          <title>Ghost Writer</title>
          <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Neil Thraves</author>
          <link>https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/gpt-2/</link>
          <guid>https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/gpt-2/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/gpt-2/">&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https:&#x2F;&#x2F;talktotransformer.com&#x2F;&quot;&gt;GPT-2&lt;&#x2F;a&gt; rewrites &lt;a href=&quot;&#x2F;other&#x2F;2017&#x2F;12&#x2F;25&#x2F;qvd.html&quot;&gt;‘Diplomacy Is For Mugs’&lt;&#x2F;a&gt;.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Queen Victoria resumed the conversation with the bottle she’d lifted from the diner. The sherry might taste of crap but it at least wasn’t a good judge of character. Bad deeds need an easy audience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Glock had been taken from the arm of a dead man, the pistol had been dropped from a plane in the middle of nowhere, and even the bottle was covered in the fingerprints of criminals. No one needed a bottle to tell them they were going down.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;Are you the one who just came to tell me about how you were going to steal a gun?&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The voice was familiar, but it didn’t sound familiar at the same time. She nodded. &quot;I’m the one who just told you about the other things I have planned. I’m going to kill your family and then go back to my hotel.&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;You aren&#x27;t going to kill my family?&quot;&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&quot;No.&quot; She held the bottle to her lips&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
      <item>
          <title>Diplomacy Is For Mugs</title>
          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
          <author>Neil Thraves</author>
          <link>https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/qvd/</link>
          <guid>https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/qvd/</guid>
          <description xml:base="https://orbitofdeceit.github.io/posts/qvd/">&lt;p&gt;Queen Victoria resumed the conversation with the bottle she&#x27;d lifted from the diner. The sherry might taste of crap but it at least wasn&#x27;t a good judge of character. Bad deeds need an easy audience.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Glock lay on the desk like a Christmas present waiting to be wrapped. Was it enough or should she pack the lead sceptre?&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Victoria slipped two spare clips for the Glock into her corset. Diplomacy was for mugs.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No-one told Queens to be silent.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The sherry agreed.&lt;&#x2F;p&gt;
</description>
      </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
